Harry Styles will perform a
30-night residency at Madison Square
Garden.  Let's talk to the fans about
how far they traveled and how much they
spent to be here.
November 16th.
52.
30.
Eight.    I
really love him.
From the top 1%.
Oh, wow.
Fan by association, but a big fan.  It's
incredible.
One Direction, and I've followed Harry
Styles ever since.
From the north of the state.
Jacksonville, Florida.
New Jersey.
I live in San Francisco.
Las Vegas.
Colorado.
Delaware.
Harlem.
500, 600.
1,300 dollars each.
Yes, she didn't want to tell me that price
for a while.
129.
They cost about 1,200 each.
More than I'd like to spend.
It's my birthday.  My dad bought them
at the last minute.
$408.
Our first time.    This
is the first time I've seen him live,
so I'm very excited.    Twice
.
I think this will be my fourteenth time
30 times means
you can probably watch it at least once.
Yes, it seemed like it would be cheaper for
him, so the tickets could have been
lower, but they weren't.
He does it for his band.
His bandmates have started
families.  I think it's a bit
inaccessible to others since it's in
New York.
You know, it took years of preparation since he's been
here since 2022.
Harry!
Come on, son.  Yes.
Everyone comes here.
Prince has done it here.  Obviously,
Billy Joel, Springsteen.
Madison Square Garden is so
special, so why not?
I'm really excited to see the next
generation of pop music fans.
See Harry Styles.
Kiwi.
Kiwi.  I hope that stays on the setlist
.
See my man.  Girl.
That's my man.